conforums.com 2016-03-05

# Conforums.com - Free Message Boards & Free Forums, Privacy Policy

Conforums has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Conforums, and is not applicable to third-party websites, that may have potential privacy policy differences and practices.  By using our website Conforums.com, you agree to and merit the understanding of Conforums' Privacy Policy in its entirety. If the user does not agree to Conforums' Privacy Policy and does not wish to be bound by its policy, it is the user's responsibility to no longer operate and immediately leave the Conforums' website. Each time a user uses the Conforums website, the current posted Privacy Policy will apply and it is the user's responsibility to review any changes since the last time a user has used the Conforums website. Policy Modification Agreement is further explained below. 

**1\. SERVER LOGGED INFORMATION**  
Whenever a user views a page located on Conforums.com, the Apache Web server automatically logs certain information about the visitor. This information includes the user's IP address, browser, and where the user came from. This is standard information collected by most Web servers. 

**1a.** Cookies  
A "Cookie", or web cookie, is a piece of information stored on a user's computer by the user's web browser. A user's browser provides this cookie whenever the user visit Conforums' website. This website utilizes cookies to store usernames and passwords for message boards that are visited. When logging into a board, all users has the option to set the length in time for the cookie to last, or to let the cookie last indefinitely. When logged into a board, the user's nickname for the user's account will be displayed in the "Users Online" section of the message board the user is at. If a user does not wish the use of cookies, it is the user's responsibility to set his/her browser preferences to not allow cookies before operating Conforums' website. It is also the user's understanding that certain features and functionality of the Conforums website may not function properly if the preference of denying cookies is implemented. 

**1b.** IP Addresses  
IP addresses are logged for Conforums to analyze traffic and data to help Conforums continually improve the user experience and to display relevant advertising content. When users post a message to a forum hosted by Conforums, the user's IP address is automatically logged with your post. The administrator of the forum you are posting in has the option to have IP addresses displayed publicly when reading the posts in the forum. 

**2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION**  
For user's to operate the Conforums website, users will be asked for personal information that identifies the user. This information includes, and is not limited to, the user's name, email address, Web site name, and web site URL. When the sign up process has completed, our script automatically logs the IP address into the user's profile as well. In addition, demographics, such as date of birth and gender will be asked to help Conforums ensure that all users are of suitable and appropriate age to be operating the Conforums website. All information collected is from the user only and not any other outside sources. 

**3\. PUBLIC DISCLOSURE**  
Please keep in mind that any information that is disclosed in forums hosted by Conforums becomes public information. Users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information. Users also have the option to provide additional personal information in user profiles that may become public information. Be aware that user profiles are publically accessible. 

Opinions in messages posted in any forums located on our service are not necessarily the views of Conforums.com. Conforums.com maintains no liability for any legal action resulting from postings in forums located on our service. 

**4\. CONFORUMS DISCLOSURE PRACTICES**  
Personal information collected by Conforums is not disclosed to third parties. 

**5\. EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS**  
Registering with the Conforums website, you consent to receiving periodic emails regarding Conforums related services and information. 

Registering with the Conforums website, in particular with other Conforums communities, you consent to receiving electronic communication from Conforums members and administrator from Conforums communities. 

**6\. MESSAGE BOARD MONITORING**  
Conforums reserves the right to monitor any and all message boards located on our server. Our staff has access to login to every password protected board to view the contents of those boards, as well as the ability to remove posts and/or boards that are found in violation of Conforums' [Terms of Service](http://www.conforums.com/tos.html). 

**7\. PRIVACY POLICY MODIFICATION OF AGREEMENT**  
This agreement may be modified and updated, without notice, at any time at the sole discretion of the Provider (Conforums.com) simply by posting the updated version of the Privacy Policy on this page. Any modification and/or update of the Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the new policy on this page. 

Last Revision: April 8th, 2011
